<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pavi&#39;s Corner of the Internet</title>
    <link>https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pavi&#39;s Corner of the Internet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shivanahalli Water Sapling Trip</title>
      <link>https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/shivanahalli-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/shivanahalli-trip/</guid>
      <description>This was an article I Wrote during my time as a volunteer at Rotaract BMSCE.
The long trip to Shivanahalli Ashram, lasted almost 2 hours. Shivanahalli, as the name suggests is a quaint little village, which most deforesters have thankfully not discovered. The Ashram, run by RAMAKRISHNA MISSION, has grown more than 3000 trees in an area which was barren before they control. The purpose of our visit there was to help the Ashram in their legitimate efforts to make a greener India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports day at Ramana Maharishi School For The Blind</title>
      <link>https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/sports-day-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paviraghunathan.com/blog/sports-day-blind/</guid>
      <description>This was an article I Wrote during my time in Rotaract BMSCE.
Sports day at Ramana Maharishi School For The Blind.
&amp;ldquo;Om sahana vavatu. sahanao bhunaktu. sahaveeryam karavavahai&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.shanti shanti shanti hi&amp;rdquo; rang through the walls of Ramana Maharishi School for the Blind as we entered the school quadrangle on the morning of 8th November,2014.
A visually impaired teacher briefed our 20 member volunteer base about the school.The school caters to the needs of visually impaired( both complete and partial) and mentally challenged children providing them with food, accommodation and education.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>